// export const data = [
//   {
//     question: "Which device is required for the Internet connection?",
//     options: ["Modem", "Router", "LAN Cable", "Pen Drive"],
//     ans: 0,
//   },
//   {
//     question: "Which continent has the highest number of countries?",
//     options: ["Asia", "Europe", "North America", "Africa"],
//     ans: 3,
//   },
//   {
//     question: "Junk e-mail is also called?",
//     options: ["Spam", "Fake", "Archived", "Bin"],
//     ans: 0,
//   },
//   {
//     question: "A computer cannot BOOT if it does not have the?",
//     options: ["Application Software", "Internet", "Operating System", "Mouse"],
//     ans: 2,
//   },
//   {
//     question: "First page of Website is termed as?",
//     options: ["Index Page", "Homepage", "Sitemap", "Pen Drive"],
//     ans: 1,
//   },
// ];

export const data = [
  {
    question: "Which device is required for the Internet connection?",
    options: {0: "Modem", 1: "Router", 2: "LAN Cable", 3: "Pen Drive"},
    ans: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "Which continent has the highest number of countries?",
    options: {0: "Asia", 1: "Europe", 2: "North America", 3: "Africa"},
    ans: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "Junk e-mail is also called?",
    options: {0: "Spam", 1: "Fake", 2: "Archived", 3: "Bin"},
    ans: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "A computer cannot BOOT if it does not have the?",
    options: {0: "Application Software", 1: "Internet", 2: "Operating System", 3: "Mouse"},
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "First page of Website is termed as?",
    options: {0: "Index Page", 1: "Homepage", 2: "Sitemap", 3: "Pen Drive"},
    ans: 1,
  },
];
